Well, it's official.
Fall is here.
Right?
Right?!
Yeah.
Just when we've overcome the pool crisis...
We now face a new challenge, Miyamura-kun.
We do, President.
It's like they're holding a wake.
I'm here at last!
And I've brought the team
assignments for sports day!
Wait, huh?
Ba-dump Ba-dump
Ba-dump
This is where I turn 'em in, right?
Yes...
As each class brings in their forms,
I feel sports day creeping closer and closer.
That's not just a feeling.
It really is getting closer.
AAAAAAAAAAGH
A rain dance!
Rain dance! Rain dance!
Excuse me! Here are our team assignments...
What's going on?!
Cooking Class
Does each class decide team
assignments by drawing lots?
East
West
Boys & Girls
(Half)
Katagiri High Sports Day Teams Splitting
To keep the number of boys and
girls balanced on each team,
East
West
Boys & Girls
(Half)
each class first divides into boys
and girls, then assigns teams.
I expect most of them only draw
for which team they'll be on.
It must feel pretty weird to be
going up against your own classmates.
Yeah, I'm glad we're on
the same team, Ishikawa-kun.
By the way, what team are you on, Sengoku?
East.
West
Why are you cheering?
Don't act so relieved!
Sengoku.
I'm counting on you.
Seriously?
Wait.
So you and Miyamura-kun split up?
We did not split up. I oughta deck you.
I meant for sports day.
I'm not going to lose to Toru and Miyamura.
Okay. Good luck to you.
Good luck to us.
Yuki and Iura are on our team, too.
Way too excited for sports day
Seriously?
That means I won't be able to
stay out of sight and do nothing...
You just casually made a pretty
loaded confession, President.
I thought he was absent,
but he was staying out of sight?
Say, the girls are gonna do
a cheer routine this year, right?
Will you be participating, Sakura?
I will.
It's mandatory.
For everyone. Even if they
have no sense of rhythm.
Your voice sounds awfully low today...
We'll need to make pom-poms.
Indeed.
I hope the steps aren't too difficult.
Are you east or west, Kono-san?
I'm on the west team.
So is Remi.
I guess that makes us rivals.
Toru and Miyamura are west, too.
I'm on the same team as Ishikawa-kun...
Last year's nightmare
And he's going to see me out
there flailing like an idiot!
Rain dance! Do a rain dance!
Okay, Sakura, we'll do one together!
Rain! Rain!
Is the student council okay?
Honestly, Sengoku's always been clumsy...
but as the council president,
he needs to get it together.
I guess he's never been much of an athlete.
Pretty much. I remember him
tripping and crying a lot.
Came home covered in dirt
after running amok at sports day
He could learn a thing or two from Sota.
Huh? Oh...
Y'know...
I don't have any fond memories
of sports days either.
You're a good runner,
so enter the 100-meter dash.
But...
No buts!
Give us everything you've got!
I'll be doing the same.
Absolutely no slacking. Or else!
I'm not really an athlete myself,
but I think it'll be more fun than last year.
Call it a hunch.
So I should do my best
in the 100-meter dash?
Your absolute best.
And I should cheer a lot?
As much as you can.
Will you cheer for me?
Of course I will!
We're on different teams, though.
I...
I know that.
But I'll still be watching.
Okay.
How strange.
I used to wish it would
be over as soon as possible,
but now I'm actually looking forward to it.
Yo, Miyamura! Can I swing by
tomorrow evening?
No, I'm getting ready for sports day.
We did ours in June.
What are you entering? Or are you skipping?
I haven't decided,
but I might do the 100-meter dash.
Whoa.
You sound surprisingly motivated.
Yeah. I surprisingly am.
Nice.
I might just come watch!
Don't, jerk.
I think the days ahead
will be a little more lively than usual.
That's enough for today. Good work!
This is hard.
I'm the only one having
trouble with the moves.
At this rate, I'll make
a fool of myself this year, too.
And this year...
And this year, Ishikawa-kun
might be watching.
Kono-san?
Yoshikawa-san?
What's the matter?
A-Are you not feeling well?
No, that's not it!
So it's something else? Are you okay?
We were just practicing our cheer routine.
Wait, was there cheer practice today?
Oh, I'm on the west team.
Gotcha. I'm east.
I'm not athletic,
and I have no sense of rhythm...
so it's really getting the better of me.
I'm sorry! It's nothing.
I'll practice a little more.
Right. Left.
Left. Right.
W-Wait, was it left? Um...
Is that the part both teams do?
Huh?
Right!
When your right hand goes up,
put your left to your chest.
Do it with me now.
O-Okay.
Hit the other side twice.
Then turn a little and throw a punch!
Th-Throw a punch.
Then put your hands up
and shake, shake, shake.
One, two, three, four!
One, two, three, four...
Right, left... Shake, shake, shake!
Why are they practicing when
they're on different teams?
I'd rather not do the cheer.
You've got this, Kono-san!
D-Do I?
Well, as long as they're having fun.
I like Sengoku-kun and Remi.
I really do.
All you had to do was mix.
You're angry.
Whether I'm angry or not
isn't the point right now.
Should I add this?
Potato Starch
Hold it, Remi! That's not right!
Read the label!
That's the wrong thing. You need this, Remi.
Worcestershire
No! Sengoku-kun, stop!
You don't add that now!
Did you read the recipe?
Watch what you're doing!
Sakura, this says "salt." Is it salt?
Cooking Salt
Salt
If it says salt, then it usually is!
You're making too big a mess
when you mix things!
Sengoku-kun's group is
still mixing ingredients.
Class is nearly over.
Never mind. Sengoku-kun, chop the vegetables.
You can handle that, right?
Huh? Chop? Me?
Peel it first!
Oops, I forgot.
How can you not see the skin is still on?
What about Remi?
That's not how you hold it!
No more knives for you!
But I want to chop vegetables.
Not right now.
That's already going to give me nightmares.
Just stir this slowly and carefully.
And don't do anything else.
Just stir it? Okay!
Ow
Ow.
I cut myself.
I need a bandage...
Wait. You need to wash it first, Sengoku-kun.
Oh, right.
Now let's go get you a bandage.
Sakura, is this stirred enough?
Hey, Sakura?
I'll put some of that stuff in.
Huh?
Hey, it's getting all wibbly.
Are you done yet?
Sakura, does this look right?
Why is it smoking?!
W-We need ventilation!
What is this? It's getting in my eyes!
Open the windows!
That's... how our last cooking class went.
Look at me.
You're angry.
Look at me so you understand!
What are we making today?
Curry.
That's right.
What ingredients did you bring?
A daikon.
Daikon Radish
Why?!
Tofu.
Tofu
Why?!
Sengoku-kun, when you have curry at
home, is there daikon in it?
No, I don't think so.
Then why did you bring one?
I've only seen curry once
it's already in a pot.
I wasn't sure what to start with.
With the vegetables you usually see in curry.
Ah!
Does placing vegetables around
the pot bring forth the curry?
You cook them!
The class picked curry so that
you two would be able to do this.
Okay, tell me what you can make.
Pasta.
Croquettes.
Warming up prepackaged food
does not count as "making" it.
I-I know!
Let's start by chipping
the vegetables I brought—
Ah! No knives for you, Remi!
And you be careful, Sengoku-kun.
H-He's gotten better!
Wow, Sengoku-kun, you're doing great!
That's it. Just peel off the skin—
The missing potato...
The potato disappeared!
Why did you pare away the whole thing?
The missing onion...
The onion disappeared, too!
You're not supposed to peel it to nothing!
Well, the class thought this might happen
and each group shared some of their
curry with us. Isn't that great?
They know us too well.
Sengoku-kun, warm up the curry.
Remi, plate the rice.
Will I never be able to cook?
If you work hard,
I'm sure you will someday.
The stove! Why are the flames so high?
It was on high heat?
High heat? That was high heat?
What did you do?
Sakura...
I'm... I'm s... I'm s-s-sorry...
The rice I made turned into gruel...
Don't cry.
Let it go.
Rice gruel will work fine, right?
Y-Yeah.
Soupy rice gruel and gooey curry...
L-Let's eat.
Hey, it's pretty good.
It's good, Remi.
Yeah, but the rice isn't cooked all the way...
Thank you guys, too.
Nah, don't worry about it.
I hope things turn out better next time.
Sakura, I'm sorry.
I mess everything up.
It's okay. Everyone has things
they're not good at.
You'll make a great wife, Sakura.
Huh? That takes much more than just cooking.
But it's still better if you can cook.
What should I do?
No one will want to marry me.
Me either.
No one will want me.
You'll be fine.
If no one wants you, I'll marry you both.
Thank you, Sakura! You're so cool!
Kono-san is boyfriend material.
Ta-da! Sports day T-shirts!
The west shirts are over there.
This is a medium size.
Need a medium, Miyamura?
Huh? A large.
Maybe a small?
Those are for girls.
No mercy for the west team!
Jeez, Miyamura.
You're such a pushover.
Absolutely no slacking. Or else!
Then you're a pushover-over, Yoshikawa-san.
That's too many overs!
Hey, Yoshikawa.
Got an extra west shirt in large?
Sure do.
You're on the committee, Toru,
so give me a hand.
Yoshikawa-san,
do you have a small east shirt?
Yoshikawa, where are the west mediums?
Yuki-chan, do you have a west small?
For crying out loud...
Just get them yourselves!
Whoa!
By the way, what'd you enter, Miyamura?
Hmm... The 100-meter, I think.
You should be in the relay.
No, that's too much pressure!
That's just for the track team.
Not really. Shu did it as a first-year.
Track Team
Though the track team did smoke him.
Uh...
Well, the other team has the president.
Yeah, that really improves
our chances of winning.
I hope he comes to sports day.
He should at least come to school.
This is our last sports day.
The president may
cease to exist that day
Rain!
All of the boys have to do the mock
cavalry battle and topple-the-pole.
The other events are coed.
Cheer practice looks pretty hard.
Hori-san will be cheering too, right?
You look great, Hori-san!
So cool!
Really?
That decides it!
How do you think I look, Miyamura?
It's complicated.
Huh?
It's not what I pictured.
And in this sentence,
this noun gets modified...
so make sure not to get confused.
Monstrous
Rage
Wh-What gives, Hori?
Deathly Chill
Haunting Aura
Ghostly rapping!
Now read the next sentence, Hori.
"It's mine."
You can ease up on the emotion a bit.
How would you translate that?
Get away from her, idiot.
Where does it say that?
She just forgot her textbook.
Yeah? That so?
Yes!
I was just showing her mine.
Hey!
Oh no!
"Oh no" what?!
You're angry at me, Hori-san.
Y-You don't need to be scared.
I haven't said anything.
I have nothing to hide. I swear.
But... I wasn't worried about that!
I just...
Never mind.
You're scary when you get jealous, Hori.
Jealous?
I wasn't feeling jealous.
It was more like murderous.
Maybe you should stick
to jealousy from now on.
Was it just you?
Were you the only one feeling jealous?
Oh, well...
Things I can say to reassure her
Maybe he just
doesn't show it.
I'm sure he's
jealous deep down.
You're too
jealous, Hori!
Don't sweat it!
All guys are
like that!
Don't sweat it!
Thanks...
Hey, it's Hori-san.
Miyamura?
And Toru!
You've even got Yoshikawa.
You almost done painting?
Just about.
They called a meeting for the sports day
committee third-years over the intercom.
They said to come as soon as you can.
What? But I'm not quite finished.
I can wrap up the painting.
Thanks—
Hori, what was your grade in art class?
Why bring that up?
Just get going already.
Thanks! I'll be back right after the meeting.
I just need to paint inside the lines, right?
Easy enough.
Yuki was worried for nothing.
I wish I had worn my blazer.
Hori, aren't you cold out here?
Mizouchi.
Yeah, I'm cold.
Girls have to put up with bare legs.
Keep that over your lap.
It won't be as bad.
You can return it when you're done.
Wait, Mizouchi!
I might get paint on it.
Hori-san!
You done?
You startled me.
I'm not done yet.
Whose is that?
Mizouchi's.
I said my legs were cold,
and he let me borrow it.
This is warmer than a blazer.
Because I've been wearing it.
Thanks.
You're gonna wear it?!
He'll never know.
Maybe, but...
Want to help me, Miyamura?
It's my first time using paint like this.
Wait, isn't that...
Destroying
the evidence
Hori.
You done?
Oh, yeah.
Thanks.
Not cold anymore?
Nope.
Let me know if you need anything.
I hope Mizouchi-kun just keeps walking
and will never know the difference
between your body heat and mine.
Honestly...
Are you jealous?
You are!
What are you giggling about?
She had it on her lap,
but the sleeves are warm?
Next time
page.3 Sports Day